safecart.com 2016-06-02

# SafeCart - Privacy Policy

RevenueWire Inc. ("RevenueWire") is committed to protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information you may provide to us when using any of our online services including without limitation, the SafeCart payment processing system ("SafeCart"). This Privacy Policy describes how we treat information we receive when you transmit data to RevenueWire. This privacy policy applies to www.safecart.com owned and operated by Revenuewire, Inc.

Revenuewire, Inc. has received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this Privacy Statement and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program. In order to view our relationship with TRUSTe please visit the validation page visible by clicking on the TRUSTe seal. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this Web site, [www.safecart.com](https://www.safecart.com/).

In order to view our relationship with TRUSTe please visit the validation page visible by clicking on the TRUSTe seal. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>

#### Shopping Cart

SafeCart is a service used by RevenueWire partnership companies. When you make a purchase you will be taken to support.safecart.com to finalize the purchase. The information we collect on this portion of the site belongs to our customers and we only collect it to process it for them. We do not use this information for any other purposes unless as described in this privacy policy.

Our checkout page collects credit card information from the user who is purchasing a product from one of our merchants. This includes credit card number, expiration date, name, Zip/Postal code, and email address. This information is used to create a login account for users who want to see their receipt for the transaction which can be accessed through support.safecart.com.

"SAFECART'S WEBSITE IS OPERATED AND MAINTAINED AS PART OF OUR ONGOING BUSINESS OPERATIONS. The information we collect here is used to collect and reply to service questions. The information collected here MAY INCLUDE YOUR BUSINESS NAME, YOUR PERSONAL name, email address, order ID number, and TELEPHONE number. You may also submit your email address or order ID number and postal/zip code to the web site in order to access and review a purchase made through the SafeCart checkout process or manage your subscriptions. You have the ability to access your personally identifiable information for the purpose of updating or deleting it by emailing us at [customerservice@safecart.com](mailto:customerservice@safecart.com) or by sending us an email through the "Contact Us" page on [support.safecart.com](https://support.safecart.com/)". We will respond to these requests within a reasonable timeframe.

We will retain your personally identifiable information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your personally identifiable information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### How Information Is Used When Collected

We may use information collected in the following ways:

  * To process, validate and verify purchases through SafeCart and other online RevenueWire services.
  * To ensure proper payments to applicable business partners such as affiliates, advertisers, or software publishers.
  * To contact you to reconfirm or verify accuracy of the information provided by you.
  * To register you as a client and open an account for you with RevenueWire either as a merchant or affiliate partner.
  * To open and maintain a support account for you.
  * To send email notifications about updates to existing product offerings, or to inform you of new product offerings or services.
  * To send information on special offers, or to obtain your feedback to help enhance existing features or provide added products and services.
  * To enable you to personalize content, advertising and promotions based on preferences, needs, suggestions, or recommendations.
  * To conduct applicable business such as invoicing or making payments to business partners.
  * To contact you should there be any changes to your SafeCart account.
  * To enforce our service agreement or terms of use.
  * As part of the process of managing information collected at support.safecart.com and using it to perform the above intended uses, SafeCart may share the information with third-party service providers. This sharing is solely for facilitating the above intended purposes and entails that all third parties protect information collected at support.safecart.com and use it only as directed and in accordance with this policy.
  * If required to be disclosed by applicable law.

SafeCart will NOT rent, share, or trade any of your personal information unless as otherwise disclosed in this privacy policy.

#### Applicable Law

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

We may also disclose your personal information if SafeCart is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

#### Emails

Any promotional emails or newsletters sent to you from RevenueWire can be opted out of by sending an email to [customerservice@safecart.com](mailto:customerservice@safecart.com). You may also fill out a "Contact Us" form on the support.safecart.com web site describing your request to discontinue our promotional email service. We will send you service and support related emails that have to do with account information or purchase orders. You cannot opt-out of receiving these service emails.

#### Tracking Technologies

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We do link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you.

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Revenuewire, Inc. and our partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember users' settings, and for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

We use Local Storage Objects such as HTML5 to store [content information and preferences.] Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs.

#### Links

We may offer links from our website to other third party websites which may be hosted by our business partners or by unrelated companies which we think may be of interest to you. Such websites are not governed by this privacy policy and we make no representation or warranties as to their practices for dealing with your personally identifiable information. We recommend that you check the privacy policy of any website at the beginning of your visit.

#### Security

The personally identifiable information that is collected and stored in limited access servers. We take reasonable precautions to protect the information that has been collected, and to safeguard the servers where such information is stored. In cases where you are subject to recurring subscription based billing (on a per use, monthly or annual basis) we will keep your credit card and personally identifiable information for no more than ninety (90) days following the day you cancel the subscription for which the recurring bills are issued. When we collect credit card information through our shopping cart, we use SSL Encryption to secure that sensitive information as it is transferred through SafeCart to our payment processor.

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at privacy@safecart.com.

#### Policy Modifications

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will notify you of any changes to this privacy policy by posting policy update notifications on the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a prominent notice on our home page prior to the change becoming effective.

#### Acceptance of Terms

By using the SafeCart services or accessing the SafeCart web site you are consenting to the practices relating to information collection and use that are described in this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at [privacy@safecart.com.](mailto:privacy@safecart.com.)

Alternatively, you may contact us by mail at:

RevenueWire, Inc.  
102-3962 Borden St.  
Victoria, BC V8P 3H8  
Canada

This privacy policy was last modified 04/18/2016

### SafeCart.com Terms of Use

Last updated: June 24, 2015

Safecart.com provides this web site (the **“Site”** ) and the services available to you through this Site (the **“Service”** ) subject to your compliance with the terms and conditions below that are binding between you and the Company (the **“Agreement”** ).

For the purposes of this Agreement, the term “Company” varies depending on where you are located. If you are located in the United Kingdom or in a member state of the European Union, “Company” means Revenuewire (UK) Ltd., a U.K. company having a registered address at Burlington House Grange Drive, Hedge End, Southampton, England SO30 2AF. If you are located elsewhere, “Company” means Revenuewire Inc., a company incorporated under the laws of Canada and having its principal place of business at 3962 Borden Street, Suite 102, Victoria, British Columbia, Canada V8P 3H8, and an address for delivery in the United States at 800 P. Street, Suite 300, Lincoln, NE 68501-3234, USA.

PLEASE READ THIS BEFORE ACCESSING THE SITE. BY ACCESSING THE SITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS BELOW. IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, YOU MAY NOT USE THE SITE.

  1. ## Rules.

While visiting the Site, you may not:

    * post, transmit or otherwise distribute information constituting or encouraging conduct that would constitute a criminal offense or give rise to civil liability, or otherwise use the Site in a manner which is contrary to law or would serve to restrict or inhibit any other user from using or enjoying the Site or the Internet;
    * post or transmit any information or software which contains a virus, cancelbot, trojan horse, worm or other similar, harmful or disruptive component; or
    * upload, post, publish, transmit, reproduce, or distribute in any way, information, software or other material obtained through the Site which is protected by copyright, or other intellectual property right, or derivative works with respect thereto, without obtaining permission of the copyright owner or right-holder.
  2. ## Site Operation

Company shall be under no obligation to continue to operate the Site for any particular term and may remove or change the Site at its sole and absolute discretion.

  3. ## Monitoring.

Company has no obligation to monitor the Site. However, you agree that Company has the right to monitor the Site electronically from time to time and to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or other governmental request, to operate the Site properly, or to protect itself or its users in accordance with Company's Privacy Policy. Company will not intentionally monitor or disclose any private electronic-mail message unless required by law. Company reserves the right to refuse to post or to remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, that, in its sole discretion, are unacceptable, undesirable, or in violation of this Agreement.

  4. ## Submissions.

All information submitted to Company through Site shall become the property of Company and Company shall be free to use, for any purpose, idea, concepts, know-how or techniques contained in in formation that you may submit to the Company through this Site. Company shall not be under an obligation of confidentiality in respect of such information except and to the extent that Company enters into or assists in establishing a customer relationship with or for you, or as otherwise agreed by Company or as may be required by applicable law. This provision shall not serve to limit the responsibilities of Company in respect of customers with whom or for whom it has established a customer relationship by, for example, referring such a customer to a payment processor or acquiring bank.

  5. ## Privacy.

Any and all non-public personal information collected through the Site will be handled in accordance with the Company privacy policy posted on the Site.

  6. ## Company Services.

Company is in the business of selling certain software keys and services, as described more fully on the Site (collectively, **“Company Products”** ). There may be specific terms and conditions of use associated with Company Products which you are required to adhere to in your use thereof. For example, but without limitation, where a Company Product is a key to access third party software, that software will be subject to an end user license agreement between you and such third party; we are not party to such third party agreements and you shall retain sole and exclusive liability thereunder and shall indemnify and hold Company harmless from and against any liabilities arising therefrom or in relation thereto.

  7. ## Third Party Billing.

Company is party to agency / payment processing agreements with certain third parties that are sellers of certain products and services (such third parties being **“Third Party Merchants”** , such products and services being **“Third Party Products”** and such agreements being **“Payment Processing Agreements”** ). Where a Third Party Merchant has referred you to the Site to pay for a Third Party Product, that Third Party Merchant is accepting your payment by way of Company as agent for the Third Party Merchant under the Payment Processing Agreement. Any payment made by you to a Third Party Merchant by way of Company as their agent shall result in you obtaining full entitlement to the Third Party Product as of when such payment is made and not as of that later time when Company releases the funds to the Third Party Merchant.

  8. ## Payments.

Company accepts payments for Company Products through the Site by means described on the Site. Payments to Company through the Site shall be inclusive of applicable sales taxes. If you have chosen to pay by credit card, debit card or prepaid card, you are authorizing a payment on that card in the amount specified. By making a payment through this Site, you are permitting your payment account information; your name; and information inputted on this Site concerning the product or service for which you are making a payment to be used to assist Company or Third Party Merchant in receiving payment of the amount you wish to pay through a payment processor. Company will not use your non-public personal information for any other purpose. Company, or the Third Party Merchant, have the right to refuse any payment you may make through the services described above. If you have made a payment in error or an over-payment or have any questions concerning Company or a Third Party Merchant, please contact us, or the Third Party Merchant in question as soon as possible.

  9. ## Limitation of Liability.

**COMPANY, INCLUDING ITS AFFILIATES, RELATED COMPANIES, SPONSORING BANKS, PROCESSORS AND OTHER SUPPLIERS, TAKE NO RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE ACCURACY OR VALIDITY OF ANY CLAIMS OR STATEMENTS CONTAINED IN THE SITE. FURTHER, COMPANY MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT THE SUITABILITY OF ANY OF THE INFORMATION CONTAINED ON THE SITE FOR ANY PURPOSE. ALL SUCH INFORMATION, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION IMAGES, VIDEOS AND OTHER DOCUMENTATION IS PROVIDED "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND. IN NO EVENT SHALL COMPANY BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OR PERFORMANCE OF INFORMATION, COMPANY PRODUCTS, OR OTHER PRODUCTS OR SERVICES AVAILABLE ON OR THROUGH THE SITE. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL THE COMPANY BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY AMOUNT GREATER THAN THE AMOUNT YOU HAVE PAID TO THE COMPANY.**

  10. ## Recourse.

If you are dissatisfied with the Site or with any terms, conditions, rules, policies, guidelines or practices of Company in operating the Site, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using the Site.

  11. ## Indemnity.

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold Company and its affiliates and related companies harmless from any and all liabilities, costs and expenses, including reasonable attorneys' fees, related to any violation of this Agreement by you or users of your account, or in connection with the use of the Site or the Internet or the placement or transmission of any message, information, software or other materials on the Site or on the Internet by you or users of your account.

  12. ## Intellectual Property.

All elements of the Site (the **"Elements"** ) such as, without limiting the generality of the foregoing, the texts, articles, photos, illustrations, images, videos and audio materials, are the property of Company and are subject to licenses or agreements allowing their broadcast through the site. No site Element may be copied, reproduced, distributed, published, translated, downloaded, posted or sent, in any way whatsoever, without the prior written approval of Company or the copyright holder. You are allowed to post or download the site Elements, but solely for non-commercial purposes and for personal use, provided you do not change these Elements and maintain all their intellectual property notices.

The trademarks and logos used or posted on the Site are trademarks which were registered or not by Company or third parties. Nothing in the Site may be interpreted as allowing, directly or indirectly, the use of a trademark reproduced on Site without the prior written approval of the owner of such trademark.

  13. ## Third Party Links

Third parties may provide links to other internet websites or resources on this Site. Company neither controls nor endorses such 'linked sites' nor have we reviewed or approved the content or information that appears on these linked sites. You acknowledge and agree that Company is not responsible for the legality, accuracy or appropriate nature of any content, advertising, products or any other materials on or available from such linked sites. You further acknowledge, and agree that Company, its officers, directors, employees, affiliates nor any other representatives shall not be held responsible, or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage, or loss caused, or alleged to be caused, by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such content, goods and services available on or through any such linked sites.

  14. ## Territory.

The Site originates and is published in Victoria, British Columbia, however, certain services offered from this Site are offered elsewhere. Company is owned and operated by RevenueWire Inc., a Canadian company having its principal place of business at 102-3962 Borden Street, Victoria, BC, Canada V8P 3H8.

  15. ## Amendments.

Company reserves the right to amend this Agreement at any time and without notice. Such changes shall be binding on you if you continue to use the Site. Please review this Agreement from time to time to see that you are in agreement with the terms hereof, such as they may be from time to time.

  16. ## Miscellaneous.

This Agreement, including any and all documents referenced herein, constitutes the entire agreement between Company and you pertaining to the subject matter hereof. In the event that you are solicited by the Company for a product or service and you wish to procure such product or service then the application for and supply of such product or service shall be governed by additional terms and conditions separate and apart from this Agreement. Company's failure to insist upon or enforce strict performance of any provision of this Agreement shall not be construed as a waiver of any provisions or right. Nothing in this Agreement shall be construed as constituting a partnership, joint venture or other association of any kind, or agent/principal relationship between the parties hereto. If any of the provisions contained in this Agreement were determined to be void, invalid or otherwise unenforceable by a court of competent jurisdiction, such determination shall not affect the remaining provisions contained herein. This Agreement shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the applicable laws of the Province of British Columbia and the federal laws of Canada applicable therein. The parties agree that any and all issues in dispute under this Agreement must be resolved exclusively by arbitration before a single arbitrator who is a practicing corporate lawyer in Victoria, British Columbia under the Commercial Arbitration Act, R.S.B.C. 1996. The parties agree that the decision of the arbitrator will be final and binding and will not be subject to appeal on a question of fact, law or mixed fact and law. The parties agree to share equally the costs of the arbitration, which costs will not include costs incurred by a party for representation by counsel.

  17. ## Contacting Company.

If you have any questions concerning this Agreement, please contact Company through the contact information set out on the Site.
